[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What were you doing right up to the moment you saw this man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "doing", "right", "up", "to", "the", "moment", "you", "saw", "this", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "I was -- I'm an executive, and I've run several companies, but I've taken time off to be with my children.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "'m", "an", "executive", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "run", "several", "companies", ",", "but", "I", "'ve", "taken", "time", "off", "to", "be", "with", "my", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "And that's why I was in the area.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "why", "I", "was", "in", "the", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "There you were, you were just driving along on your way to an audition and then suddenly, you see what?", "question_tokens": ["There", "you", "were", ",", "you", "were", "just", "driving", "along", "on", "your", "way", "to", "an", "audition", "and", "then", "suddenly", ",", "you", "see", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I turn the corner and what I saw was a man with black hair in a Kevlar vest with a black shirt and a rifle standing on the corner, on the left-hand corner, motioning a girl in her car to come forward.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "turn", "the", "corner", "and", "what", "I", "saw", "was", "a", "man", "with", "black", "hair", "in", "a", "Kevlar", "vest", "with", "a", "black", "shirt", "and", "a", "rifle", "standing", "on", "the", "corner", ",", "on", "the", "left-hand", "corner", ",", "motioning", "a", "girl", "in", "her", "car", "to", "come", "forward", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "And, Russell, I mean, what was the first that you heard about this?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Russell", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "was", "the", "first", "that", "you", "heard", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "I'm sitting in my office, my phone rings, it says my wife is calling, I pick it up, expecting a normal conversation about what time I'm going to be home and what we're going to do with the kids that night.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sitting", "in", "my", "office", ",", "my", "phone", "rings", ",", "it", "says", "my", "wife", "is", "calling", ",", "I", "pick", "it", "up", ",", "expecting", "a", "normal", "conversation", "about", "what", "time", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "be", "home", "and", "what", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "with", "the", "kids", "that", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Russell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Debra, I mean, what kind of gun was he using?", "question_tokens": ["Debra", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "gun", "was", "he", "using", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "He had an automatic rifle.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "an", "automatic", "rifle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "When you come face to face with that, had you ever as a couple had much thought about guns before this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "come", "face", "to", "face", "with", "that", ",", "had", "you", "ever", "as", "a", "couple", "had", "much", "thought", "about", "guns", "before", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "I know a bit about guns and I have shotguns at a range, so I know what they look like, but I've never seen somebody out on the street with an automatic rifle the way it was -- it was aimed at first the girl that he hijacked and then myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "a", "bit", "about", "guns", "and", "I", "have", "shotguns", "at", "a", "range", ",", "so", "I", "know", "what", "they", "look", "like", ",", "but", "I", "'ve", "never", "seen", "somebody", "out", "on", "the", "street", "with", "an", "automatic", "rifle", "the", "way", "it", "was", "--", "it", "was", "aimed", "at", "first", "the", "girl", "that", "he", "hijacked", "and", "then", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "They fire incredibly quickly, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "fire", "incredibly", "quickly", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "They fire incredibly quickly.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "fire", "incredibly", "quickly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "You must feel incredibly lucky to be alive, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "feel", "incredibly", "lucky", "to", "be", "alive", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I feel very lucky to be alive.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "very", "lucky", "to", "be", "alive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Would you be prepared to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "prepared", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I would love to meet up with her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "to", "meet", "up", "with", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "But nobody in Washington seems to care enough to do something about it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "nobody", "in", "Washington", "seems", "to", "care", "enough", "to", "do", "something", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "I've always been very neutral in terms of gun control.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "always", "been", "very", "neutral", "in", "terms", "of", "gun", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Snowden"]}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What is your reaction to Edward Snowden's decision to leak this information?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "Edward", "Snowden", "'s", "decision", "to", "leak", "this", "information", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I think Mr. Snowden had no right to arrogate to himself the right to decide where to strike the balance between liberty and security.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Mr.", "Snowden", "had", "no", "right", "to", "arrogate", "to", "himself", "the", "right", "to", "decide", "where", "to", "strike", "the", "balance", "between", "liberty", "and", "security", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hezbollah", "Hezbollah"]}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What do you believe the consequences of his decision could be at their worst?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "believe", "the", "consequences", "of", "his", "decision", "could", "be", "at", "their", "worst", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, the problem is, that once you start explaining to al Qaeda and Hezbollah how you are operating, they can avoid what you're doing, and you can't explain to the American people without explaining to Hezbollah and al Qaeda.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "problem", "is", ",", "that", "once", "you", "start", "explaining", "to", "al", "Qaeda", "and", "Hezbollah", "how", "you", "are", "operating", ",", "they", "can", "avoid", "what", "you", "'re", "doing", ",", "and", "you", "ca", "n't", "explain", "to", "the", "American", "people", "without", "explaining", "to", "Hezbollah", "and", "al", "Qaeda", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Why should they?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "OOLSEY: Well, they don't know everything about your online activity, because it's illegal --", "answer_tokens": ["OOLSEY", ":", "Well", ",", "they", "do", "n't", "know", "everything", "about", "your", "online", "activity", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "illegal", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "But they could, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "they", "could", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "It's illegal for them to take some steps with respect to it such as to get into the substance of the -- of the intercept.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "illegal", "for", "them", "to", "take", "some", "steps", "with", "respect", "to", "it", "such", "as", "to", "get", "into", "the", "substance", "of", "the", "--", "of", "the", "intercept", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "You are a supporter of Edward Snowden and his actions, why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "a", "supporter", "of", "Edward", "Snowden", "and", "his", "actions", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, from what I hear and what he's done, I mean, he's done a great service because he's telling the truth and this is what we are starved for.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "from", "what", "I", "hear", "and", "what", "he", "'s", "done", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "'s", "done", "a", "great", "service", "because", "he", "'s", "telling", "the", "truth", "and", "this", "is", "what", "we", "are", "starved", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "It's palpably a breach, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "palpably", "a", "breach", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, it depends on whether or not you want to preserve your country's ability to operate in a world of terrorism in which a lot of terrorist are very technically sophisticated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "depends", "on", "whether", "or", "not", "you", "want", "to", "preserve", "your", "country", "'s", "ability", "to", "operate", "in", "a", "world", "of", "terrorism", "in", "which", "a", "lot", "of", "terrorist", "are", "very", "technically", "sophisticated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "-- 99.9 percent of the information being effectively seized here?", "question_tokens": ["--", "99.9", "percent", "of", "the", "information", "being", "effectively", "seized", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Given the fact that this system was put together by the people's elected representatives that it's been upheld by the courts.", "answer_tokens": ["Given", "the", "fact", "that", "this", "system", "was", "put", "together", "by", "the", "people", "'s", "elected", "representatives", "that", "it", "'s", "been", "upheld", "by", "the", "courts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["99.9 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "They both have to be considered and you apparently -- Piers, not to want to consider security?", "question_tokens": ["They", "both", "have", "to", "be", "considered", "and", "you", "apparently", "--", "Piers", ",", "not", "to", "want", "to", "consider", "security", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "NNPS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No, no, I absolutely do want to consider it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "I", "absolutely", "do", "want", "to", "consider", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "If you had been president, are you in all seriousness telling me that you would have stopped all of this tracking of data in the way that the NSA has been doing it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "been", "president", ",", "are", "you", "in", "all", "seriousness", "telling", "me", "that", "you", "would", "have", "stopped", "all", "of", "this", "tracking", "of", "data", "in", "the", "way", "that", "the", "NSA", "has", "been", "doing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "AUL: An awful lot of it, but it wouldn't be stopped.", "answer_tokens": ["AUL", ":", "An", "awful", "lot", "of", "it", ",", "but", "it", "would", "n't", "be", "stopped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NSA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 308, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Well, I just --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "just", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Jeffrey Toobin, is anything that's happened here illegal?", "question_tokens": ["Jeffrey", "Toobin", ",", "is", "anything", "that", "'s", "happened", "here", "illegal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Certainly not, as far as we can tell.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "not", ",", "as", "far", "as", "we", "can", "tell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffrey Toobin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "But after the Gateway legislation called the Patriot Act, as an American I think anybody living in this country isn't any expectation of privacy and personal, you know, security -- isn't that really a moot point, the whole discussion about having any kind of privacy?", "question_tokens": ["But", "after", "the", "Gateway", "legislation", "called", "the", "Patriot", "Act", ",", "as", "an", "American", "I", "think", "anybody", "living", "in", "this", "country", "is", "n't", "any", "expectation", "of", "privacy", "and", "personal", ",", "you", "know", ",", "security", "--", "is", "n't", "that", "really", "a", "moot", "point", ",", "the", "whole", "discussion", "about", "having", "any", "kind", "of", "privacy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "That is a really good point.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "a", "really", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Well, basically, Ron Paul the president, would he utilize the information that was collected to prevent another 9/11 or what would he use in place of it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "basically", ",", "Ron", "Paul", "the", "president", ",", "would", "he", "utilize", "the", "information", "that", "was", "collected", "to", "prevent", "another", "9/11", "or", "what", "would", "he", "use", "in", "place", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "I think that's pretty much a red herring, I mean, it's nonsense.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "pretty", "much", "a", "red", "herring", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "nonsense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "How does that serve the American public interest?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "serve", "the", "American", "public", "interest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, there's no -- there's been no accusation at all that he's handing any kind of information to China.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "--", "there", "'s", "been", "no", "accusation", "at", "all", "that", "he", "'s", "handing", "any", "kind", "of", "information", "to", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "-NONE-", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "But what is to stop -- what is to stop the Chinese doing that should they so wish if they get a hold of him first?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "to", "stop", "--", "what", "is", "to", "stop", "the", "Chinese", "doing", "that", "should", "they", "so", "wish", "if", "they", "get", "a", "hold", "of", "him", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "I mean, that's an interesting question, but I think it side- steps a real issue, which is that he showed that the United States was violating multiple laws in both the Patriot Act and the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "interesting", "question", ",", "but", "I", "think", "it", "side-", "steps", "a", "real", "issue", ",", "which", "is", "that", "he", "showed", "that", "the", "United", "States", "was", "violating", "multiple", "laws", "in", "both", "the", "Patriot", "Act", "and", "the", "Foreign", "Intelligence", "Surveillance", "Act", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "I mean, is he just a -- collection of metadata, like they claim, or can the people at the sharp end, and there are 1.4 million Americans currently working intelligence in some way who have that kind of access -- can they read e-mails, listen to phone calls, et cetera?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "he", "just", "a", "--", "collection", "of", "metadata", ",", "like", "they", "claim", ",", "or", "can", "the", "people", "at", "the", "sharp", "end", ",", "and", "there", "are", "1.4", "million", "Americans", "currently", "working", "intelligence", "in", "some", "way", "who", "have", "that", "kind", "of", "access", "--", "can", "they", "read", "e-mails", ",", "listen", "to", "phone", "calls", ",", "et", "cetera", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yes, they can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]